Finding Aid for E. B. Muller and Company (Port Huron, Mich.) records, 1902-1937
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
E. B. Muller and Company (Port Huron, Mich.) records 1902-1937
E. B. Muller and Company (Port Huron, Mich.).
1 linear foot and 6 oversize volumes.
852067 Bb 2; BB Outsize
Chicory processors of Port Huron, Michigan. Warehouse inventories, acreage and seed reports, manufacturing records, journals, ledgers, and miscellaneous papers.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Gordon McMorran (donor no. 3540 ) and came to the library in 1959.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The E. B. Muller and Company was a chicory processing business based in Port Huron, Michigan.
The record groups includes business correspondence, warehouse inventories, acreage and seed reports, financial journal and ledgers, and miscellaneous other records.
Subjects:
Business records.; Chicory.; Port Huron (Mich.)
Contributors:
Muller, E. B.
- Business records
  - Correspondence and other papers,1902-1937 and undated
    - Undated (Box 1)
    - 1902-1905 (Box 1)
    - 1910-1914 (Box 1)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 1)
    - 1920-1928 (Box 1)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 1)
  - Warehouse Inventories, 1925-1937
    - 1925-1926 (Box 1)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 1)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 1)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 1)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 1)
    - 1937 (Box 1)
  - Acreage and Seed Reports
    - 1917-1927 (Box 1)
    - 1928-1936 (Box 1)
  - Manufacturing Records, 1925-1936, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Unpaid ledger balances, 1934, 5 folders (Box 1)
  - Financial journals, June 1910-January 1926
    - June 1910-February 1912 (Volume 1)
    - October 1915-September 1919 (Volume 2)
    - October 1919-January 1926 (Volume 3)
  - Financial ledgers, October 1910-September 1913
    - October 1910-September 1911 (Volume 4)
    - October 1911-September 1912 (Volume 5)
    - October 1912-September 1913 (Volume 6)